(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-27T14:08:38.482167",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
open sesame, let's go out drinking la la la
so excited, sing along & shake a body !
so excited, sing along & shake a body!
open sesame, let's go out drinking la la la
so excited !
so excited!
冷蔵庫から こんばんは
Good evening from the refrigerator!
水のように清らかに、太陽のようにみんなを照らす
"Pure like water, illuminating everyone like the sun,"
サントリー公式バーチャルユーチューバーのサントリーノムです！
"I'm Suntory's official Virtual YouTuber, Suntory Nomu!"
はーい！
"Hi!"
本日はサントリーノムプレゼンツウィンターミニライブということで、素敵なゲストの方々が来ております。
"Today, for the Suntory Nomu Presents Winter Mini Live, we have some wonderful guests joining us."
それではまず、そらちゃんから自己紹介をお願いいたします！
"First, Sora-chan, please introduce yourself!"
はーい！皆さんこんにちは！ときのそらです。
"Hi! Hello everyone! I'm Tokino Sora."
本日はこんな素敵なライブにゲスト出演させていただいて、とっても嬉しいなって思っています。
"I'm so happy to be participating as a guest in such a wonderful live today."
本日は、どうぞよろしくお願いします！
"Thank you very much for having me today!"
はーい！
"Hi!"
よろしくお願いしまーす！
"Looking forward to it!"
さあ、続いてはじめましてのラミィちゃんお願いいたします！
"Now, next, Lamy-chan, who is making her first appearance, please!"
はーい！はじめまして、ホロライブの雪花ラミィと申します。
"Hi! Nice to meet you, I'm Yukihana Lamy from Hololive."
いやもうすごい緊張してるんですけど、今日は楽しんでいこうと思いますのでよろしくお願いします！
"Um, I'm super nervous, but I plan on having a great time today, so nice to meet you!"
よろしくお願いいたします！
"Nice to meet you too!"
いや、ラミィちゃん初めましてなんですが、もし、ラミィちゃんとお呼びしてもよろしいでしょうか？
"Um, Lamy-chan, since it's our first time meeting, would it be okay if I called you 'Lamy-chan'?"
もちろんですよ！ノムちゃんって呼んでもいいですか？
"Of course! Can I call you Nomu-chan?"
あ、もちろんですよ！ありがとうございます！
"Ah, of course! Thank you so much!"
そらちゃんもいつも通りノムちゃんと…
"Sora-chan, as always, Nomu-chan and..."
ノムちゃんよろしくね！よろしくお願いいたします！
"Nomu-chan, nice to work with you! Looking forward to it!"
はい、いや、本日は素敵なお二人と楽しんでライブをしてまいります。
"Yes, well, today I'll be enjoying and doing the live with these two wonderful people."
そらちゃんとは以前にも歌ってみたを一緒に歌わせていただいたり色々こうご一緒させていただく機会があったんですが、本日のライブの意気込みをお伺いしてもよろしいでしょうか？
"With Sora-chan, we've had opportunities to sing together on covers and other things before, but could you tell us your enthusiasm for today's live?"
はい、もう、久しぶりにね、ノムちゃんと一緒に、そしてね、後輩のラミィちゃんと一緒にこう、ライブに出られるということで、
"Yes, well, for the first time in a while, being able to perform live together with Nomu-chan and our junior Lamy-chan,"
今日はね、テンションが高まっています！なので、なんかみんなに素敵な
"today my tension is high! So, I want to deliver wonderful"
音楽をプレゼントできるように、そして、楽しいミニライブになるように頑張ります！よろしくお願いします！
"music to everyone, and make it a fun mini live! Please look forward to it!"
はーい！よろしくお願いいたしまーす！ありがとうございます！
"Hi! Looking forward to it! Thank you so much!"
さあ、ラミィちゃん！ラミィちゃんも本当に本日のライブに本当ぴったりということで、ありがとうございます！今回お招きできて光栄なんですが、ラミィちゃんの意気込みをお伺いしてもよろしいでしょうか？
"Now, Lamy-chan! Lamy-chan is also really a perfect fit for today's live, thank you! We're honored to have you invited this time, could we hear your enthusiasm for today's live?"
はい！今日はね、もう本当にさっきも言ったんですけど、ライブ、ミニライブにね参加させていただけても今本当にもドキドキがすごいんですけど、
"Yes! Today, as I said before, being able to participate in a live, a mini live, my heart is pounding so much right now,"
そら先輩とはノムちゃんといっぱい笑顔で楽しんでいきたいと思います！頑張ります！ありがとうございます！
"I want to enjoy it with plenty of smiles alongside Sora-senpai and Nomu-chan! I'll do my best! Thank you!"
はーい！本日は3人で素敵なライブをお届けしたいと思います。
"Hi! Today the three of us would like to deliver a wonderful live."
えー、1つですね、お詫びと訂正がございまして、
"Um, there is one apology and correction,"
サントリーノムのTwitterにて、あのハッシュタグが、え、そらゆきノムライブと記載されていたんですが、改めてまして、あのライブの感想などはぜひ、ハッシュタグノムライブにてお願いいたします！
"on Suntory Nomu's Twitter, the hashtag was listed as 'SoraYukiNomuLive', but once again, please send your thoughts on the live using the hashtag #NomuLive!"
よろしくお願いします！お願いします！
"Please look forward to it! Please!"
はい、たくさんコメントも来ておりますかね！ありがとうございます！
"Yes, lots of comments are coming in too! Thank you so much!"
はい、それでは早速なんですけれども、私からトップバッターを切らせていただきたいと思います！
"Yes, then without further ado, I would like to kick things off as the first batter!"
はい！そらちゃんラミィちゃんの素敵な歌も続きますので、本日は最後までお楽しみください！
"Yes! Sora-chan and Lamy-chan's wonderful songs will continue, so please enjoy until the very end today!"
え、それではステージとマイクの設定に少しお時間をいただきますので、皆様も少々お待ちくださーい！
"Um, then we will take a little time to set up the stage and microphone, so everyone please wait just a moment!"
ただいまセッティング中です しばらくお待ちください
"We are currently setting up. Please wait a moment."
まるで映画みたい
"Like something out of a movie,"
目にうつる銀世界
"A silver world reflecting in my eyes."
いっそ時間を止めて
"If only we could stop time,"
永遠に夢のなかへ
"And stay in a dream forever."
冬の空は澄んで
"The winter sky is clear,"
息を白く染めて
"Dyeing our breath white."
足跡が残るようにと
"Wanting our footsteps to remain,"
わざわざ靴を汚したの
"I purposely got my shoes dirty."
「オヤスミ。」
“Good night.”
ねぇ ママ いつ夢の続きでいい
Hey, Mama, whenever is fine in a dream...
人ゴミにまぎれても
...even if I get lost in the crowd.
同じ空見てるのに
Even though we're looking at the same sky,
風に吹かれてて
blown by the wind.
もっと波のこえるのに
Even though we have to cross even more waves,
僕は 君のすべてなど
I don't need to know
知っては いないだろう
everything about you, do I?
それでも 一億円から
Even so, from 100 million...
君を見つけたよ
I found you.
根拠はないけど
Though there's no basis for it,
本気で思ってるんだ
I really mean it.
ささやかな愛もなくって
With no trivial love either,
ララライ ララライ 同じ時間を 生きてなどいけない
lalalai lalalai we can't live out the same time.
素直に なれないなら
If you can't be honest,
よろこびも哀しみも
joy and sorrow alike...
無駄にしていくだけ
will just go to waste.
こんな雪ね 心まで白く染められたなら ahaha 二人の孤独を分け合うことができたのかな
If this snow could dye even my heart white, ahaha, could we have shared our solitude?
僕は 君の心に
I push my ears
耳を押しあてて
against your heart,
その声のする方へ すうっと深くまで 降りてゆきたい
and want to descend deep into the direction of that voice.
そこでもう一度会おう
Let's meet there once more.
わかり合いたいなんて
Even if I want us to understand each other,
ララライ ララライ 腕をなでて
lalalai lalalai caressing your arm...
痛いのは 僕の方よ
It's my heart that hurts,
握りしめることだけで 繋がってた
connected by merely gripping tightly.
こんな雪ね 永遠を前に あまりにもろく ahaha ざらつく
If this snow is so fragile before eternity, ahaha, rough...
アスファルトの上 シミになっていくよ
becoming a stain on the asphalt.
こんな雪ね 時により頼りなく 心は揺れる
If this snow is sometimes unreliable and makes my heart sway...
こんな雪ね 心まで白く染められたなら ahaha 2人のこと 守り続けたい
If this snow could dye even my heart white, ahaha, I want to keep protecting the two of us.
こんな雪ね 心まで白く染められたなら ahaha 二人の
If this snow could dye even my heart white, ahaha, the two of us...
孤独をくるんで 空に返すがら
wrapping our solitude and returning it to the sky...
鏡 よ 鏡
Mirror, oh mirror,
真実 の わたし を 映し出 し て
reflect my true self,
本当 の わたし らし さ を 取り戻 さ せ て
and let me take back
that's so dope ! so cool !
that's so dope! so cool!
you , too ! just kidding !
you, too! just kidding!
最高 の 気分 な の
I'm in the highest of spirits!
大好き な 服 着 て
Wearing my favorite clothes,
鏡 の 真前 で クルクル 回る わたし
spinning around right in front of the mirror.
イエベ じゃ ない 知っ てる けど
I know it's not trendy,
オレンジ の 気分 な の
but I'm in an orange mood.
マニュアル 通り なんて
Just following the manual?
退屈 じゃ ない ？
Isn't that boring?
あー しろ こー しろ とか
Ah, dressing like this or that...
外野 は もう イヤイヤ な の
The outside world is already annoying.
自分 こそ が 中心 だって
Believing that I myself am the center,
信じる 人 の ところ で 世界 は 回る
the world revolves around the one you trust.
真夜中 鏡 の 真前
Right in front of the mirror at midnight,
わたし は 自由
I am free.
一番 自然 な 笑顔 浮かびん じゃ う
The most natural smile floats to the surface.
わたし は わたし で 良い の
I'm fine just being myself,
そっと ウインク し て ポーズ とる の
giving a subtle wink and striking a pose.
that's so dope ! so cool !
that's so dope! so cool!
you , too ! just kidding !
you, too! just kidding!
演じる の 嫌い じゃ ない
It's not that I hate acting,
勿論 苦手 じゃ ない
of course, it's not that I'm bad at it either.
欲しがり 過ぎない で よ もう
Don't be too greedy,
自分自身 忘れ ちゃう でしょ
or you'll forget who you really are.
nana na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na...
意味 なんて ない 方 が 好き の lululu lulu
I like it better when it makes no sense.
nana na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na...
お隣 さん は 多分 「 良い 人 だ と 思う 」
The neighbor is probably "a nice person."
お酒 は いらない の よ
I don't need any alcohol;
自分 に 酔う 才能 なら ある
if I have the talent to get drunk on myself.
愛 は 飲め ば 飲む ほど に 増えて いく もの なん だって
They say love only grows the more you drink it,
空き缶 も 出ない し
so not even an empty can is left behind.
違う の ナシスト じゃ ない
No, that's not being a narcissist,
むしろ 真逆
quite the opposite,
だから メタル を ストレッチ し て いる
I'm just stretching my mental state.
鏡 の 向こう の わたし
The "me" on the other side of the mirror,
あなた が 好き その 素肌 も
"I love that bare skin of yours."
どうして な の もう 泣かない で よ だって
What is it? Don't cry now,
あなた は そう よ 頑張って 来 た じゃ ない わたし は 知っ て いる 全部
you've worked so hard, I know it all.
真夜中 鏡 の 真前
Right in front of the mirror at midnight,
わたし は 自由
I am free.
一番 自然 な 笑顔 浮かびん じゃ う
The most natural smile floats to the surface.
わたし は わたし で 良い の
I'm fine just being myself,
そっと ウインク し て ポーズ とる の
giving a subtle wink and striking a pose.
that's so dope ! so cool !
that's so dope! so cool!
you , too ! just kidding !
you, too! just kidding!
鏡 よ 鏡
Mirror, oh mirror,
真実 の わたし を 映し出 し て
reflect my true self,
本当 の わたし らし さ を 取り戻 さ せ て
and let me take back
that's so dope ! so cool !
that's so dope! so cool!
you , too ! just kidding !
you, too! just kidding!
最高 の 気分 な の
I'm in the highest of spirits!
大好き な 服 着 て
Wearing my favorite clothes,
鏡 の 真前 で クルクル 回る わたし
spinning around right in front of the mirror.
イエベ じゃ ない 知っ てる けど
I know it's not trendy,
オレンジ の 気分 な の
but I'm in an orange mood.
マニュアル 通り なんて
Just following the manual?
退屈 じゃ ない ？
Isn't that boring?
あー しろ こー しろ とか
Ah, dressing like this or that...
外野 は もう イヤイヤ な の
The outside world is already annoying.
自分 こそ が 中心 だって
Believing that I myself am the center,
信じる 人 の ところ で 世界 は 回る
the world revolves around the one you trust.
真夜中 鏡 の 真前
Right in front of the mirror at midnight,
わたし は 自由
I am free.
一番 自然 な 笑顔 浮かびん じゃ う
The most natural smile floats to the surface.
わたし は わたし で 良い の
I'm fine just being myself,
そっと ウインク し て ポーズ とる の
giving a subtle wink and striking a pose.
that's so dope ! so cool !
that's so dope! so cool!
you , too ! just kidding !
you, too! just kidding!
演じる の 嫌い じゃ ない
It's not that I hate acting,
勿論 苦手 じゃ ない
of course, it's not that I'm bad at it either.
欲しがり 過ぎない で よ もう
Don't be too greedy,
自分自身 忘れ ちゃう でしょ
or you'll forget who you really are.
nana na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na...
意味 なんて ない 方 が 好き の lululu lulu
I like it better when it makes no sense.
nana na na na na na na
Na na na na na na na...
お隣 さん は 多分 「 良い 人 だ と 思う 」
The neighbor is probably "a nice person."
お酒 は いらない の よ
I don't need any alcohol;
自分 に 酔う 才能 なら ある
if I have the talent to get drunk on myself.
愛 は 飲め ば 飲む ほど に 増えて いく もの なん だって
They say love only grows the more you drink it,
空き缶 も 出ない し
so not even an empty can is left behind.
違う の ナシスト じゃ ない
No, that's not being a narcissist,
むしろ 真逆
quite the opposite,
だから メタル を ストレッチ し て いる
I'm just stretching my mental state.
鏡 の 向こう の わたし
The "me" on the other side of the mirror,
あなた が 好き その 素肌 も
"I love that bare skin of yours."
どうして な の もう 泣かない で よ だって
What is it? Don't cry now,
あなた は そう よ 頑張って 来 た じゃ ない わたし は 知っ て いる 全部
you've worked so hard, I know it all.
真夜中 鏡 の 真前
Right in front of the mirror at midnight,
わたし は 自由
I am free.
生まれて初めて書いたのはなんて字だったかな 初めて描いた似顔絵は誰の顔だったんだろう
Even the writing I first did when I was born, I wonder whose face it was...
不思議だねもうずいぶん書き留めてきたけど
It's strange, I've been writing things down for quite a while now,
最初の一筆は緊張しちゃうな
but the very first stroke still makes me nervous.
きっとなにかが世界を救う
Surely something will save the world,
絶対いつか出会えるはずなの
I'm sure we'll meet someday.
沈む夕日に 寂しくひとり
All alone as the setting sun sinks,
拳握り締める 私
I clench my fist tightly.
宇宙規模しか 時間のフレックス
Space-scale flex time,
相手はどこにでもいるんだから
Because the other person is anywhere.
今夜の深海 期待している
Looking forward to tonight's deep sea,
友達の友達に
With a friend of a friend,
目立つにはどうしたらいいの
How should I stand out?
一番の悩み
My number one worry.
性格良ければいい
As long as my personality is good,
そんなの嘘だと思いません？
Don't you think that's a lie?
Twinkle Star 幸せの予感
Twinkle Star, a premonition of happiness,
きっとなにかを感じてる
Surely feeling someone.
Lonely love ロマンスの神様
Lonely love, the god of romance,
この人でしょうか
Could this be the person?
ノリと勢い 必要みたいなの
It seems like momentum and mood are necessary.
初対面の男の人って
When meeting a guy for the first time,
年齢 住所 趣味に職業
Age, address, hobbies, occupation,
さりげなくチェックしなくちゃ
I have to casually check them all.
マジで今シタ 合格ライン
Seriously, did I pass the qualification line right now?
早くサングラス取って見せてよ
Hurry up and take off your sunglasses to show me.
笑顔も素敵 素顔も素敵
Your smile is wonderful, your bare face is wonderful,
思わず見とれてしまうの
It makes me gaze at you without realizing.
幸せ見られるものならば
If happiness is something to be seen,
友情より愛情
Love rather than friendship.
コーヒーを奢ってくれて
Buying me coffee,
ちょっと信じられない
I can hardly believe it.
Twinkle Star 恋してる瞬間
Twinkle Star, the moment I fall in love,
きっとあなたを感じてる
I'm sure I'm feeling you.
Lonely love ロマンスの神様
Lonely love, the god of romance,
願いを叶えて
Grant my wish.
Twinkle Star 恋してる気持ち
Twinkle Star, the feeling of love,
なんだかんだ言って素敵な宝物だからな
Because it's such a wonderful treasure after all.
Lonely love ロマンスの神様どうもありがとう
Lonely love, thank you so much, god of romance.
よく当たる星占いにも
Even in the accurate horoscope,
そう言えば書いてあった
Now that I think of it, it was written there.
今日会う人と結ばれる
I'll be tied to the person I meet today.
今週も来週も再来週もずっと
This week, next week, the week after next, forever,
Twinkle Star
恋してる瞬間きっとあなたを感じてる
The moment I fall in love, I'm sure I'm feeling you.
Lonely love ロマンスの神様願いを叶えて
Lonely love, god of romance, grant my wish.
土曜日遊園地 1年経ったら結婚しよう
Saturday, amusement park—if a year passes, let's get married!
Lonely love ロマンスの神様感謝しています
Lonely love, god of romance, I am grateful.
いつまでもずっとこの気持ちを忘れたくない
I never want to forget this feeling forever.
Lonely love ロマンスの神様
Lonely love, god of romance,
いつまでもずっとこの気持ちを忘れたくない
I never want to forget this feeling forever.
Lonely love ロマンスの神様どうもありがとう
Lonely love, thank you so much, god of romance.
燦鳥ノライブ presents ウィンターライブ mini
ただいまセッティング中です しばらくお待ちください
[Santorin Live presents Winter Live Mini
We are currently setting up. Please wait a moment.]
皆さん、お疲れ様でした！
Everyone, thank you for your hard work!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
さて、後半もまだまだライブは続きますが、その前に少し休憩いたしましょう！
Now then, the live performance will continue, but let's take a short break first!
はい！
Yes!
後ろにあのペットボトルをご用意させていただいておりますので、そちらのドリンクをお求めください。
We've prepared plastic bottles behind us, so please grab your drink from there.
ペットボトルだー！やったー！
Plastic bottles! Yay!
さあ、たくさんありますわよ。
Now, there are plenty of them.
え？どれにしようかな？
Eh? Which one should I choose?
いっぱい！いっぱいありますよ。
There are tons! There are so many.
私はこちらや…
Mine is over here...
えーっと、これ？これにします！
Um, this one? I'll take this!
それでは…では、乾杯いたしましょうか。
Well then... Shall we have a toast?
はい！
Yes!
はい！いきますよ、せーの！
Yes! Here we go, ready, set!
乾杯ー！
Cheers!
ああ、染みるー！染みわたるー！
Ah, it hits the spot! So refreshing!
ああー、美味しい。
Ahh, delicious.
美味しいですよねー。
It really is delicious.
で、皆様からのコメントありがとうございます！「ありがとうございまーす！」「ありがとうございます！」
And thank you for all your comments! "Thank you so much!" "Thank you!"
皆様からの、ね？感想などもお聞きしたいなと思うんですけども。ね？さっとも…
I'd love to hear your impressions too, you know? Satto-mo...
ありがとうございます、乾杯乾杯と。はい！
Thank you for all the cheers! Yes!
よかった！美味しいですよねー。
Yay! It's so good, right?
何か、他に気になるコメントなどありますでしょうか？
Are there any other interesting comments?
飲む飲むタイムということで、飲むタイム！ありがとうございます。
Drinking time! "Drinking time!" Thank you very much.
さて、ウインターミニライブまだまだ続くんですけれども、実はここで皆様にお伝えしたいことがございまして…
Now, the Winter Mini Live continues, but actually we have something important to tell everyone...
なんですか？はい！
What is it? Yes!
先ほど飲んでいただいたドリンクなんですが、実は１人だけ違う飲み物はなんであります？えー！？
The drinks you just had... actually, one of you is drinking a different beverage! Ehh?!
はい！果たしてそれが誰なのか？
Yes! Who on earth could it be?
では、今から私たちで推理していきたいなと思います。
Now, we're going to deduce who it is.
なんだって！？
What?!
なんだと！？題して、えー「違う飲み物を飲んでいるのは誰だ！？ドリンクウルフ！！」イエーイ！
What?! Entitled... "Who is drinking a different drink?! Drink Wolf!!" Yay!
え、今からですね、１人だけ、あの、違う飲み物を飲んだ人を捜し当てるのですが、単に会話をしながらですとちょっと簡単な…
So starting now, we'll try to figure out who drank the different drink, but just chatting normally might be a bit too easy...
今回はですね、カードで引いた生き物の語尾をつけて挑戦していただきたいなと思います。なるほど！なるほど！
So this time, we'd like you to challenge yourselves by adding the ending of an animal drawn on a card! I see! I see!
では、えーと、カードをその語尾のカード、さらちゃんにでは引いていただきましょう。
Now, let's have Sara-chan draw the card for the ending.
さらちゃん、お願いいたします！何の語尾があるんですかねー？
Sara-chan, please! What kind of ending will it be?
どんな語尾が…
What kind of ending...
これで、楽しみですよね。
This will be fun, right?
あ、はい！
Ah, yes!
なんてした？
What was it?
さらちゃん、カードの発表お願いいたします！
Sara-chan, please announce the card!
ドキドキ…猫！
Thumping... Cat!
あー！猫ちゃんだー！
Ahh! It's a cat!
かわいらしい！
So cute!
猫ちゃんの語尾は…にゃん！にゃん！
The cat's ending is... nyan! nyan!
そうだにゃん？そうなんだよ。にゃん！にゃん！
Is that so, nyan? That's right. Nyan! Nyan!
ですよね？はい、さあ…
Right? Yes, now...
どなたがじゃあ…あ、もう始めてよろしいんでしょうか？
Who is going to... Ah, can we start already?
よろしいにゃん！
That's fine, nyan!
よろしいにゃん！では、あの語尾の…語尾は「にゃん」で行きましょう。
That's fine, nyan! So let's use "nyan" for the ending.
はい！はいにゃん！にゃん、にゃん、にゃん！
Yes! Yes, nyan! Nyan, nyan, nyan!
それでは皆様はどなたが違う飲み物を飲んでいるのでしょうか？ということで、シンキングタイム、スタート！
Now, who among everyone is drinking a different drink? With that, thinking time, start!
イエーイ！
Yay!
スタートだにゃん！
Start, nyan!
ちなみに、どんな味でした？
By the way, what did yours taste like?
味でした？
Taste?
味は…味にゃん。味にゃん。
Taste is... taste, nyan. Taste, nyan.
えーと…さわやかだったにゃん。
Um... it was refreshing, nyan.
あ、さわやかさ、さわやかだったにゃん？さわやかなんだにゃん！
Ah, refreshing, it was refreshing, nyan? It's refreshing, nyan!
瑠美が飲んだのもさわやかだったにゃね？
What Rumi drank was also refreshing, nyan?
うん。はあー、さらちゃんは…
Yeah. Haa, Sara-chan...
さらちゃんはしゅわっとしたかニャ？
Did Sara-chan go fizz, nya?
しゅわっとしたかにゃ？
Did it go fizz, nya?
そういう聞き方はありにゃん？なしかにゃん？
Is that kind of question allowed, nyan? Or not, nya?
ちなみにしゅわっとしたかにゃん？
By the way, did it go fizz, nyan?
えと、せ、せーの、で、せーの、で、せーの、で…
Um, on three, ready, set, on three, ready, set...
せーの！
Ready, set!
どのとき飲みたいにゃ？
When do you want to drink?
まぁどんなとき、うーん
Well, when do you... um...
スカッとしたときにゃん！
When you want to feel refreshed, nya!
スカッとしたときにゃん？
When you want to feel refreshed, nya?
ああ、いい質問だにゃ。
Ah, good question, nya.
うーん、どんなとき、うーん、
Well, what kind of time... um...
スカッとしたときにゃん！
When you feel refreshed, nya!
When you want to feel refreshed, nya!
スカッとしたときに飲みたいにゃんね。
When you want to feel refreshed, nya.
こう、なんか目を覚ましたいときとか？
When you want to wake your eyes up, or...
飲みたいにゃんね。
Want to drink, nya?
そらちゃん、違うときかニャ？
Sora-chan, is that a different time, nya?
いや、でも、え、どうし、どうしてニャ？私だけが違うの？
No, but... wait, what? What's going on, nya?
それにはどんなとき、ニャ？
When is that time, nya?
お風呂とか暖かいところ行った後とかに、さっぱり飲みたいにゃんね。
Things like after a bath or somewhere warm, you want to drink it nice and crisp, nya!
そらちゃん、ラミーちゃんは違うかニャ？
Lamy-chan, isn't that different, nya?
よっ！
(Laughs)
ラミーは、
Lamy is...
やっぱり、あっさりきれいにしたいときに、あれ？あれれ？あれれれれ？
Probably when you want to feel refreshed, nya... wait, what?
あ、あ、笑ってしまいました！配信終了ですわ！
Oh, wait, I messed up! Stream's over!
あ、終了ですにゃ！
It's over, nya!
皆さん、どうでしたか、ね？
Everyone, how was it, nya?
私なんか、そらちゃんと同じようにゃ。
For me, it's just like Sora-chan's, nya!
本当にゃ！そらちゃんと同じようにゃ。
Really, nya? Just like Sora-chan, nya.
なんか、え？気がしたのニャ。
I felt it, nya.
みんな一緒に感じてしまったにゃんな！全員同じ！
Everyone felt the same, nya! We're all the same, nya!
でも、そんなことないにゃん。何しても違うにゃん。
Wait, there's no way it's different, no matter what you do, nya.
どっちかニャ？私、そうですね。
Which one is it, nya? For me... that's right.
え？なんですか？天の声、なんか、え？天の声がどうこうにゃ？
Eh? What is it? The voice of heaven? What's going on, nya?
答えを変えてくださいって。私だけが違うとかそんな、そんなことある？
Wait, change your answer! Only mine is different? Such a thing...
もしかして、天の声が訂正したにゃ？そうにゃ？そうにゃ？
Could it be that the voice of heaven changed its mind, nya?
あ、中落ちるだとかそんなのないでしょ！(笑)
There's no way you'd fall or anything, right? (Laughs)
捕まったら、そんなの、そんなの聞いてないにゃ！
If you're caught, there's no way... I haven't heard that, nya!
そんなの、そんなの微塵もなかったにゃ！
That didn't happen at all, nya!
これは、天の声から、のむちゃんが場所移動って言われた。
This is... from the voice of heaven, Nomu-chan's location moved, it said.
えー？私でしょうか？ラミーちゃん、私が哀しいと思ってるのかにゃ？
Eh? Is that me? Lamy-chan, do you think I'm pitiful, nya?
いや、もう天の声がそう言ってるにゃ！
Yeah, the voice of heaven says so, nya!
私はもう天の声を信じるにゃ！
I believe the voice of heaven, nya!
待って、待ってない！違います、深読みですわ、きっと何にか事情があるんですわ！
No, wait, it's deep-dark night, so there must be some reason, nya!
皆さんコメントどうですか？
Everyone, how are your comments, nya?
私は、私、私もよろしいですか？私は、ラミーにゃんかなあ？と、思ったらは？
As for me... is my answer okay too, Lamy-chan? What about...
ねえ、コメントの皆さんいかがですか？みんなは笑っているにゃん。
Hey, everyone in the comments, what do you think? Everyone is laughing, nya!
それでは、あの、皆さんが何を飲んだのか、誰がウルフだったのか発表させていただきます。こちらです！
Then, let's announce what everyone drank and who was a werewolf! Here it is, nya!
ぜんのー、にゃん！
Zen-no-nya!
ひどいです、私、私そんな気がしましたわ。こう場所移動で、うーん。
Terrible! I thought for sure... but it's location-based, um...
あ、なるほど、ここにタイアップが出ると、でもそれにしても私と違う。
Ah, I see! If it comes with a tie-up, but even so, mine is different.
あ、でも、そんな気がしてたにゃ。
Well, even so, I had that feeling, nya.
さっぱりしたいときにね、飲みたいにゃんね。
I wanted to drink when I wanted to feel refreshed, nya.
私もちょうでも、CCレモン飲んだような気がしてきちゃった。
I also felt like I drank C.C. Lemon, nya.
だって天然水スパークリングレモンって出てますからね、同じレモンでどっちも美味しいから難しいですよね。
Wait, C.C. Lemon is out as Sparkling Lemon, so both are delicious lemons, it's hard, nya!
ちょっとの、もう一回お願いできますか？
Can you ask, one more time, please?
次回よろしいですか？もう一戦できますか？
Is it okay next time? Can you do one more line, nya?
やった！じゃあ、もう一回行きましょう、では！
Yay! Then, let's go again, nya!
ドリンクをもう一回よろしいですか、選んで、選びましょうか。
Drink... choose again, please, and make your choice.
では、私からじゃあ、カードを引かなくて大丈夫かな？後でね、後で引くね。
Then, from me, is it okay not to draw a card? I'll draw later.
これは、そらちゃんが違うんでしょうね。きっと、そらちゃんまだ誰も飲んでない、誰も始まってないにゃん！
This must be different from Sora-chan's, for sure. Sora-chan, nobody drank yet, nobody started yet, nya!
どういうこと、にゃん？どういうこと、にゃん？どうしたの、そのボトル。
What do you mean, nya? What is that bottle?
次はそら先パイ、にゃ。
Next is Sora-senpai, nya.
さあ、そらちゃん何を選ぶんでしょうね、皆さん。
Sora-chan, what are you going to choose, everyone?
ごびもカードを引かなくてはですね。これを持って来たにゃん。
Gobi doesn't have to draw a card either, right? I brought this, nya.
きっと違うんでしょうね！なんで？なんで！
I'm sure it's different, nya! Why? Why, nya?
ラミーいきます！
I'm going with Lamy, nya!
さあ、なんでしょうね、楽しんでみなさいね！楽しんでみなさいね！
So, what is it? Have fun, everyone! Have fun, everyone!
ラミーちゃん選びましたか？あ、もう、飲みにするにゃ！はい！乾杯を、どうしましょ、乾杯をしてからカードを引きます。
Lamy-chan, did you choose? Let's toast first! Wait, should we toast first?
じゃかん、始めましょー！
Let's get started!
確かに。
True.
せーの！
Ready, set!
かんぱーい！
Cheers!
おお……。
Oh...
ん、ん、ん、ん。
Mm-hm...
あ、これは……。
Ah, this is...
濃厚しやすさー？
Rich and easy to drink?
のは？
Is it?
じゃあ、ラミィちゃんにカードを引いていただきましょうか。
Shall we have Lamy-chan draw a card?
はい、引きまーす！
Yes, I'll draw!
じゃあ、今のうちにソラちゃん何でした？
So, Sora-chan, what was yours just now?
言えないよ！言ったらダメだよ！言っちゃダメだよ！
I can't say! You mustn't say it! You really can't!
え、言わないの？
Eh, you won't say?
ラミィちゃん、はよお帰りなさーい。
Lamy-chan, welcome back.
では、ラミィちゃんどんなお味か、あの、発表してください。
Now, Lamy-chan, please announce what it tastes like.
はい！
Yes!
次の語尾は「熱血」！
The next sentence ending is "Passionate"!
熱血、熱血……。
Passionate, passionate...
熱血の、まあ、語尾というか、これはキャラじゃないですかね？
Passionate... well, rather than an ending, isn't this a character trait?
熱血キャラ。熱血キャラ！
A passionate character! A passionate character!
ははあ、なるほど！熱血キャラ。
I see, I see! A passionate character.
行くぜー！うおおお！
Let's go! Whoa!
考え抜くんだぜ！
Think it through!
そうですよねー。
That's right.
戻ってまーす！よかったねー！
I'm back! Good for you!
何を飲んだんだ？
What did you drink?
ええと……ええと、熱血の方の1、2証人って何なんでしょうか？
Um... um, what are the first two witnesses of the passionate type?
あ、そういうこと。ええと、熱血になればいいんだ！
Ah, I see. Um, you just have to be passionate!
そうですよ！語尾を、語尾を熱血っぽくすればいいんですよ！
That's right! Just make your sentence endings sound passionate!
うわ、我が輩は！
Whoa, as for this one!
すっきりだったなり！
It was refreshing, naru!
あ、シンキングタイムスタートします！
Ah, thinking time starts now!
す、す、す、スタートしたの！
It, it, it started?!
始まったぜ！始まったが！
It's started! It started, but!
どうだ？どうだぜ？
How is it? How is it?
どうだぜ？な、いや、同じくスッキリ系したと思うぜ。
How is it? No, I think it was also a refreshing type.
あ、ここいい！ここいいぜ！
Ah, this is good! This is good!
ここいいぜ！いや、どうだ？どうだ、これもスッキリしてたと思うぜ。みんな一緒だ。みんな一緒だな。
This is good! No, how about this? I think this was refreshing too. We're all the same. We're all the same.
いや、だめだ。それじゃあ、当てられないぞ、それは。
No, that won't do. You won't guess it with that.
ええと、なんかもっと特徴とか、どんな時に飲むとか、あるだろ。
Um, isn't there something more characteristic, like when you drink it?
あ、いや、うーん……食事かな？
Ah, well, um... during meals?
食後！我らは、我らは……！
After meals! We, we...
我ら、なんかもうお父っぽいな。
We sound like old men now.
食事時だな。食事時……。
At mealtime. Mealtime...
食事時ときと食後って言いました？あれ、ここなんかどちらが違うのでは？
Did you say mealtime and after meals? Wait, aren't those different?
食事中だったぜ！
It was during meals!
だぜ！熱血！もちろん！だぜ！もちろん食事中にも飲むだろ、飲むな。
That's right! Passionate! Of course! Of course you drink during meals, right?
いや、でもね、ラミィもどっちかっていうと食後だぜ、これ。
No, but you know, Lamy, this is more like after meals.
息を飲むんだぜ！黙ったな。
Hold your breath! You went quiet.
これ、立ち位置変わらなくてもいいのではないか？
Shouldn't we change our positions?
はあ、息を飲むんだぜ！
Ha, hold your breath!
他に何か、なんか、うーん、そうだな。
Anything else, um, let's see.
ヘルシーな感じがあるんだぜ！
It has a healthy feel to it!
でもヘルシーじゃないのもあるぜ？
But aren't there unhealthier ones too?
え？え？あ、あれ、ラミィちゃんこっちだぜ！
Eh? Eh? Ah, wait, Lamy-chan is on this side!
ヘルシーじゃないバージョンもあるぜ？これはない、ないぜ！
There's a non-healthy version too? This isn't it!
あんまり思い出かんないな。
I can't really remember.
あ、違うかもしれないぜ、これは！
Ah, this might be wrong!
おお、これは、これは！
Oh, this is, this is!
きっと、もしかして……。
Surely, maybe...
自主規制をするか？
Should we self-censor?
あ、でも多分、多分大丈夫なんだぜ！
Ah, but it's probably, probably fine!
立ち位置は大丈夫！もう大丈夫なんだぜ！
The position is fine! It's already fine!
この立ち位置で。
In this position.
じゃあ、ええと、資料ということなんだぜ！で！
So, um, it's about the data! And!
みんな怪しい方を刺すぜ！
Everyone point at the suspicious one!
刺すぜ！
Point!
まあ、じゃあ、じゃあ、ええと、
Well, then, um,
我が輩から、我が輩が怪しいなと思ったのは、
As for me, the one I thought was suspicious is...
ラミィちゃんだぜ！
Lamy-chan!
私も同じくラミィちゃんだぜ！
I also think it's Lamy-chan!
いやー、同じくラミィちゃんだぜ！
Yeah, I also think it's Lamy-chan!
ヘルシーっていう、ヘルシーじゃないのはない、ないぜ！
There's no such thing as a non-healthy one!
思い浮かばないんだぜ！
I can't think of any!
さあ、それではみんなが何を飲んでいたのか、誰がウルフだったのか、発表だぜ！
Now, let's announce what everyone was drinking and who the wolf was!
だぜ！
That's right!
どーん！
Ta-da!
よっしゃあ！もう確かに、これはね、クロウロンちゃんにヘルシーじゃないのはないですね！
All right! Indeed, for Kouron-chan, there's no such thing as a non-healthy one!
他の種類の…ってなって…
Other kinds... and then...
あ、やってみたぜ！
Ah, we tried it!
おいしいぜ。
It's good.
おいしかった。普通に。
It was good. Pretty normally.
おいしかった。
It was good.
やあ、やあ。そらちゃんがね、
Yeah, yeah. Sora-chan...
日清…なんだぜ？
Nissin... is that it?
そうだぜ！
That's right!
やったー！はじめてー！
Yay! First time!
おひげじゃないか。あ、そうそう。
Isn't that a mustache? Ah, right right.
なんか一緒にさ、喜んじゃったけど。やあ、やあ。彼らは楽しいですわね。ええ。
We got excited together. Yeah, yeah. They are having fun, aren't they? Yeah.
はあ、というわけで、こうやってね、あ、コメントもね、たくさんあの、来ておりますけれども、あ、さすがそらちゃんだって来てますわね。
Ha, so, like this, ah, there are also a lot of comments coming in, ah, "As expected of Sora-chan", they're saying.
さすが。
As expected.
ねえ。いや、こうやってあの、そらちゃんやラミィちゃんとこう、歌うだけでなく、あの、遊ぶことができてとっても楽しいですわね。
Right. Well, being able not just to sing with Sora-chan and Lamy-chan, but also play together is so much fun.
うん、ご覧の皆さん、お楽しみいただけましたでしょうか？だぜ、だぜ？
Yeah, hope everyone watching is enjoying it, right, right?
あ、まだそれ、引きずってる感じですか？
Ah, are you still dragging that along?
どうでした？楽しかったかな？楽しかった、楽しかった、楽しそうぜ。
How was it? Did you have fun? It was fun, fun, looks fun.
熱血！熱血、難しいですね。
Hot-blooded! Hot-blooded, it's difficult.
ブレブレだったよ。ブレブレ。「我れ」って言い始めましたもんね。
It was shaky. Shaky. You started saying "I".
一人称がちょっと難しかったんだぜ！
The first-person pronoun was a bit difficult!
そうだぜ！そうだぜ！
That's right! That's right!
ええ、たくさん、そらちゃんおめでとうと。
Yeah, "Congratulations to Sora-chan", a lot.
ありがとうございます！おめでとうございます！はい。
Thank you very much! Congratulations! Yes.
いや、それでは次のコーナーに移りたいと思いますので、いったんスタジオの準備をさせていただきます。少々お待ちくださーい！
Well then, we'll move on to the next corner, so we'll prepare the studio for a moment. Please wait a moment!
ただいまセッティング中です しばらくお待ちください
[Currently setting up. Please wait a moment.]
はい、たくさんのコメントありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you very much for all the comments!
え、続いてはこちらのコーナーにまいりましょう。お！アンケートトーーク！
Well then, let's move on to the next corner. Oh! Questionnaire Talk!
え、今からトーク内容のお題が出てきますので、ご覧の皆さんの投票でどんなお話をす るか決めておきます。チャット欄にアンケートが出てまいりますので、みなさんどんどん投票してください！
Well, from now on, topics for the talk will appear, so we'll decide what to talk about based on everyone's votes. A questionnaire will appear in the chat, so everyone please vote away!
それでは、トークテーマはこちらです。どん！出ますでしょうか？
Well then, here is the talk theme. Ta-da! Will it appear?
ええと、おすすめしたいもの、自分なりのポーズ、今年挑戦したい料理。
Let's see: something you want to recommend, your own pose, cooking you want to try this year.
なるほど。はい。この3つ。
I see. Yes. These three.
おすすめしたいもの、自分なりの決めポーズ、今年挑戦したい料理。
Something you want to recommend, your own signature pose, cooking you want to try this year.
おお。それでは皆さま投票お願いいたします！
Ooh. Well then, everyone, please cast your votes!
まず…ちょっと待ってね。
First... wait a minute.
最初のほうがよろしいでしょうか？
Would the first one be good?
いや、どれが選ばれると思います？自分なりの決めポーズってのがすごい気になるんですけど。
No, which one do you think will be chosen? I'm really curious about "your own signature pose".
なんていうか、「自分、一番いいポーズとってるポーズ、これは最高でしょう」みたいな。
Like, "Me, striking the best pose, this must be the best" kind of thing.
ええ！？これ最高…あ、いまやっちゃった？いまやっちゃった？後でもう一回やんなきゃいけなくなる。
Eh?! This is the best... Ah, did you do it just now? Did you do it just now? You'll have to do it again later.
あ、そうですよね。
Ah, that's right.
はい、じゃあアンケート、はい、開始です！みなさま投票お願いいたします！お願いしまーす！
Yes, then the questionnaire, yes, has started! Everyone, please vote! Please!
みんなはどれが聞きたいんだろうね？
I wonder which one everyone wants to hear?
今年挑戦したい料理…二人にお勧めしたいもの。
Cooking you want to try this year... something to recommend to the two of you.
みなさんどうですか？決めポーズおもしろそうとか来てますね。
How is everyone? "Signature pose sounds fun" and comments like that are coming in.
いや、これは気になる、気になりますね。トリの決めポーズ気になる。
Man, this is interesting, I'm curious. The bird's signature pose is interesting.
え、それ、それを考える…
Eh, thinking about that...
いや、それを考えるアンケートなんだ！
No, it's a questionnaire to think about that!
作る、作る。今、ちょっとおじか…今、今、今考えておきますよ、今。
Making, making. Now, little ti... Now, now, I'm thinking about it now.
ええ、ええ、考えましょう。ちょっとじゃあ繋いでくれる。
Yeah, yeah, let's think. So please keep talking.
みんな、どうかな？どうしよ、決めポーズ、じゃあちょっと二人の決めポーズ、もし決めポーズになったら、のむちゃんにやってもらいましょうよ。
Everyone, what do you think? What should we do, signature pose, well, if it becomes signature pose, let's have Nomu-chan do it.
あまりほどね？
Not too much, right?
二人の決めポーズを。確かに！
The two's signature poses. True!
さあ！
Now!
あ！はい。
Ah! Yes.
さて、締め切り終了です！
Now then, the deadline is closed!
終了です！いえーい！
Closed! Yay!
それでは結果を見てみましょう、どうぞ！
Now let's check the results, go ahead!
自分なりの決めポーズ、ラミィは果たして…
Lamy's own signature pose, I wonder if...
決めポーズ！
A signature pose!
じゃあどなたから行きますか？自信満々なラミィ…
So who's going first? Confident Lamy...
自信満々なの？
Are you confident?
自信満々だったの？
Were you confident?
え、自信満々だったって！ええ！？自信なさげだったですけど
Wait, you were confident? Huh?! You looked unconfident though!
ノウムさんにやってもらいますかね？
Shall we have Nomu-san do it?
ブイブイブイ！じゃあ
V-v-v! Then,
きっとすごく可愛いんでしょうね？みなさん
It must be super cute, right everyone?
じゃあやっぱりね、可愛いポーズやりましょうか？
So as expected, shall we do a cute pose?
はい、わあ、楽しみですわ。
Yes, wow, I'm looking forward to it.
じゃあちょっとね、ラミィのこのサムネイルの今日のサムネイルにもなっている
So now, Lamy's thumbnail, which is today's thumbnail as well,
はい、ポーズ。こちら！はい、これがラミィの決めポーズ！
Yes, pose. Here! Yes, this is Lamy's signature pose!
可愛い。コールジェーター。いいですねー。
Cute. Coordinator. That's nice.
いいね。そらちゃんもぜひ。
Nice. Sora-chan, please too.
はい、ですねー。
Yes, exactly.
これで素晴らしい！
With this, wonderful!
さあ、ありがとうございます！ガチいただいて
Now, thank you very much! Receiving it seriously
で、あ、やっぱりお一人ずつやっていく感じで
And, ah, as expected, doing it one by one
じゃあ、どうします？あ、そらちゃん先ですか？
So, what shall we do? Ah, Sora-chan first?
あ、私のは決めポーズというか、今日のやつはたぶんね、こんな感じになってると
Ah, as for my signature pose, today's one is probably, you know, looking like this
難しいと思う。これは体感が
I think it's difficult. This requires core strength
重要ですわね。
that's important.
あ、いいですねー。あとはこう前にってやってるポーズが多いかな？
Ah, that's nice. Also, I guess there are many poses reaching forward?
あ、大丈夫？
Ah, are you okay?
こんな感じで
Like this,
うーん、なるほど！すごいバランス取ってる！
Hmm, I see! You're keeping your balance so well!
ちょっと頭の中で次を考えてる？あ、なるほど！
Thinking about the next thing in your head? Ah, I see!
じゃあ行きましょうか、のむさんの決めポーズ、のむさん！
So shall we go, Nomu-san's signature pose, Nomu-san!
じゃあ、わたくしは
Well, as for me,
顔が！どんなポーズですか？かっこいい顔で！
Face! What kind of pose is that? With a cool face!
何なの、そのポーズは。
What is that pose?
これはなんでしょうね？
I wonder what this is?
さあ、じゃあ、せ、あ、せっかくなんでお二人で、急に？
Now, then, since we have this chance, the two of you—suddenly?
じゃあせーのでいきましょうか？
Then shall we go on three?
せーの！
One, two!
え、何をやるの？
Eh, what are we doing?
あ、のむさんのコネクションの？
Ah, Nomu-san's connection pose?
ですか？
Is that it?
え、のむさん、え、のむちゃんの見本をお二人で決めて、その前にお二人で一緒にやって、ちょっと説明させてください。
Eh, Nomu-san, eh, Nomu-chan's example, you two decide it, do it together first, and let us explain a bit.
なんなんですか？ノウムさんの決めポーズがひどいので、お二人で考えてあげてくださいって言われたの。
What is it? We were told that Nomu-san's signature pose is terrible, so please think of one together for her.
なるほど、なるほど。
I see, I see.
そんなひどいですか？
Is it that terrible?
いや、私たちがそういう意味かなと思って。なるほど。
No, we thought that might be what it meant. I see.
それを言いはやってた。
You were saying that.
オッケーでした。さ、
Okay then.
お二人でせーのでやって、そのふたつをやってもらおう。
Let's have the two of you do it on 'one-two'.
やってもらいましょうか。
Shall we have them do it?
ふたつともやってもらいますか。かしこまりました。
Shall we have them do both? Understood.
じゃあせーので行きましょうか？せーの！
Then shall we go on one-two? One, two!
一緒でもいいかも。
Maybe together is fine too.
ソラさんが足がこうで、あ、エレガントですよね。ラミィちゃん可愛いですよね。
Sora-san's legs like this, ah, elegant, right? Lamy-chan is cute, right?
こうで、フラフラします。
Like this, wobbling.
どうしようフラフラしちゃう。
What should I do, I'm wobbling.
なるほど。
I see.
な、こんな何がいけないんですか？
Wh-what's wrong with this?
かっこいいと思うよ。そうなんだよね。
I think it's cool. That's right.
足の安定感もありますしね、無理のない。
There's stability in the feet too, no strain.
そうですわ。
That's right.
あの、皆さまもリスナーの皆さまもやってくださいね。
Um, everyone, listeners too, please try it.
お写真撮る際はこれです。
When taking photos, this is it.
え、これですか？
Eh, is this it?
これでお願いしまーす。
Please do this.
頑張ります。
We'll do our best.
じゃあ、もういっちょもアンケートいきましょうか？
Well then, shall we go to another survey?
今のこのポーズを抜いた残りのふたつですよね。
The remaining two excluding this current pose.
はい、おすすめしたいものこと、もしくは今年挑戦したい料理。では皆さん投票お願いいたします！
Yes, things/items we recommend, or cooking we want to challenge this year. Now everyone, please vote!
さあ、おすすめ、ポーズやってる場合じゃないですね。
Now, recommendations—this isn't the time to be doing poses.
ねえ、おすすめしたいものこと、おすすめ結構範囲が広いね。
Hey, things we recommend—recommendations have quite a wide range.
でも、結構割れ、割れてますね。真ん中
Still, it's quite split. The middle
半々ぐらい？
about half and half?
半々ぐらい。
About half and half.
ねえ、皆さん何が知りたいんでしょうね？気になる。
Hey, what do you guys want to know? I'm curious.
今年挑戦したい料理じゃないですか？
Isn't it cooking you want to challenge this year?
今年挑戦したい料理、私たち。ねえ。
Cooking we want to challenge this year, us. Right.
料理しますか？あんまり
Do you cook? Not really.
のむちゃんしますか？
Nomu-chan, do you?
全くしないんですか？
You don't do it at all?
もしこれを答えることになったら、あのビーフストロガノフが食べたいです。
If it turns out answering this, um, I want to eat beef stroganoff.
よしすごい！
Awesome!
なんてすごい！
How amazing!
言うだけなら
If it's just talking,
ただだよ！
it's free!
言うだけならただだからね、そりゃね。
If it's just talking, it's free, right?
ビュー…
Bier...
言うなら！
If you say so!
急にすごいね
That's suddenly amazing.
なに？なに？
What? What?
何があったんですか？
What happened?
はい、では、こちらです！
Yes, here it is!
おすすめ！
Recommendations!
今なんのこっちゃ！
What is this about right now?!
そんなこと挑戦したい料理とか聞きましたかね今？
Did you just ask about dishes we want to try?
なんでもいっとけば大丈夫ですわ
Anything is fine as long as you say it.
挑戦したいですから。
Because we want to try it.
特に得意料理ではないので
It's not like it's our specialty,
確かに、普段は満場一致で
true, normally unanimously
ビーフストロガノフとか今おすすめしたいことですし
beef stroganoff or something is what we want to recommend now.
そうですよね？
Right?
いいえ、そうじゃないんだ。
No, that's not it.
残念ですわ！
Too bad!
残念ですね！
え、何にしましょう？おすすめしたい…
Um, what should we do? What we want to recommend...
物でも事でもいいみたいなね。
Anything, whether it's an item or a thing, is fine.
えー、物でも事でもいい。
Eh, goods or experiences are fine.
あ、じゃあ私、最近、あの購入して良かったものが…
Ah, then for me, something I bought recently that was great...
お、なんだろう。
Oh, what could it be?
あの、シルクのナイトキャップ！
Um, a silk night cap!
眠る時にかぶるの。そうすると、
You wear it when sleeping. When you do that,
あの枕との摩擦が、そのなくなるので、髪の毛が痛みにとく…
the friction with the pillow disappears, so your hair gets less damaged...
痛みに出にくいと。
and less prone to damage.
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
それを今日、えっと、２つセットで…えっ、何より？
Today, um, in a set of two... Eh, what's more?
え、買わされるんですか？
Eh, are you being made to buy it?
ぶ、ぶ、自主規制ですわ！
S-Self-censorship!
そうなんです、シルク、ナイトキャップ、シルクのナイトキャップが…
That's right, a silk nightcap, a silk nightcap is...
結構おすすめです。ラミちゃんほら
It's pretty recommended. Look, Lamy.
二人とも髪の毛可愛いので！
Both of you have cute hair!
ねえ、クルクルと巻いて入れていただいて。そうなんです、おすすめなんです、ですよね。
Hey, wrap it around and put it in. That's right, it's recommended, isn't it?
ねえ、皆さん使ってるよ、使ってるよ。
Hey, everyone's using it, using it.
いや、買ってないですね。買ってないよ！
No, I haven't bought it. I haven't bought it!
なかったことに、なかったことにして！
Let's pretend that didn't happen, pretend it didn't happen!
なかったことにして。でも、持ってる持ってる、一人もいなかったでしょ、なんなら。
Pretend it didn't happen. But you have it, nobody had it, if anything.
持ってる持ってるって言って、のむちゃんにはそう見え…私には、幻、幻なんですか、それは。
Saying you have it, to Nomu you look... to me, is it an illusion, is that it?
ねえ、残念ですが、残念ですね。
Hey, unfortunately, unfortunately.
で、何かお勧め。
So, any recommendations?
えー、ラミーは最近やってるのが、朝起きたら白湯を飲む。
Um, what Lamy has been doing lately is drinking warm water when she wakes up.
あー、いいですね！
Ah, that's nice!
なんかすごくこの咽頭が最近乾燥するので、朝起きてこうお水を飲みたいんだけど、こう冷えたものを飲むと体が、
Somehow my throat gets dry lately, so when I wake up in the morning I want to drink water, but drinking cold stuff makes the body...
そうです、成長じゃないですか。
that's right, isn't it good for metabolism?
だから、朝起きてこう白湯を1杯飲むと、すごくこう頭も起きるし、
So when you wake up in the morning and drink a cup of warm water, it wakes up your head,
喉もうるおうしで、すごくおすすめですよ。
and moisturizes your throat, so it's super recommended.
いいことしかないですよね。
There are only good things about it, right?
ほらみんな飲んでるよ、飲んでる？
Look, everyone's drinking it, right? Are you drinking?
飲んでてなかった、確かに。
Wasn't drinking at all, true.
白湯のめよ、やめてください！
Drink warm water, please stop!
で、あ、でもほら白湯いいねってありますか？
But hey, is there a "warm water is good" response?
体にいいよね。うん、いいですよね。
It's good for the body, right? Yeah, it's good.
えーと、私は、えーと、たまになんですけど、毎日やるとすごい筋肉痛になっちゃうので、
Um, for me, um, occasionally, doing it every day makes me really sore,
あんまり毎日ではないんだけど、体幹を鍛えるための、
not every day, but to train the core,
ポーズみたいなのがあって、ポーズ、うん。
there's like a pose, a pose, yeah.
で、できる？ぶっこがわなきゃいけない。
Can you do it? You have to keep your butt down.
ちょっとできるかどうかわかんないんですけど、こう、こういう、
I don't know if I can do it, but like, like this,
あ、じゃあやってみます、じゃあ、えっと、
Ah, then let's try it, then, um,
こう、お猫様がいて、で、はい、見えます？ここ？
like this, there's a cat-like pose, and, yeah, can you see? Here?
こう、お尻をつけた後に、ぐって。で、このポーズで、あのね1分以上キープするというのを、
Like this, after putting your butt down, push hard. And in this pose, holding it for over a minute,
やると結構それだけで体幹、インナーマッスルが鍛えられて、結構いい感じ。
if you do that, just that trains your core and inner muscles, it feels pretty good.
これ、のむちゃんも行きましょうよ。
Nomu-chan, let's do this too.
プランクなんて無視でいいんですわ！
Planks or whatever, just ignore them!
いやでもさ、プランクなんていいですから、もうやりますか？じゃあ。
No, but planks are fine, should we do it then?
二人ともやりましょうという。二人でやりましょう。
Both of us should do it. Let's do it together.
二人ともやりましょうって言ってんの！なるほど！
Saying both of us should do it! I see!
えーと、こうして、たかせる、はい！せーの！で、これをずっと、1分間キープするっていうのを、
Um, like this, raise it, yes! Ready, go! And keeping this for a whole minute,
3回ぐらいセットでやる。
doing about 3 sets.
え、歌うんです！
Eh, we sing!
ちょっと、歌うから！
Wait, because we sing!
あー、皆さんごきげんよう！
Ah, hello everyone!
結構でも慣れてくると、もっとできるけど、まだ、まだ歌うの？
But once you get used to it you can do more, still, you're still singing?
これ、カロリーはまだ残しとかないと。
We have to keep some calories left.
こういうのは、あの、毎日やってると、あの、腹筋とかが鍛えられて、こう、こういうプランクやり続ける時に体幹が鍛えられる。
Things like this, if you do them every day, your abs are trained, and doing planks like this builds your core.
から、さっきのポーズにつながる。さすが先輩！
So it connects to the pose earlier. As expected of senpai!
なるほどね。いや、楽しい放送でしたね。
I see. Well, it was a fun broadcast.
え、とっても楽しい。
Um, very fun.
まだ残ってますからね。まだでしたね！
It's still left. It was still there!
いや、大変でしたけれども、ね、め、め、め、め、
Well, it was tough, but, you know, m-m-m-m,
プランク、プランクでしたよね。うん、頑張りましたね。
plank, it was plank. Yeah, we did our best.
いや、皆さんのいろんな話を聞いちゃっ…さっき曲歌っ…
Well, hearing everyone's various stories... earlier we sang a song...
でも疲れてるんじゃないですか？
Aren't you tired?
そうです、そうです、色んな話を聞くことができました！
That's right, we were able to hear all sorts of stories!
はい。
Yes.
いやもっとおしゃべりしたいところではございますが、ここからいよいよライブ後半です！
Yes, we'd love to chat more, but now comes the second half of the live!
はい！
Yes!
最後までこの…歌いますでしょうか、この…大丈夫に…
Will we be singing this until the end? This... is it alright...
ね？
Right?
はい、最後までぜひお楽しみください。
Yes, please enjoy it all the way to the end.
ええと、ステージとマイクのセッティングに少々お時間をいただきますので、皆さん、もう少々お待ちください。
Um, it'll take a moment to set up the stage and microphones, so everyone, please wait just a moment.
頑張りまーす！
We'll do our best!
雫色
Droplet color,
誰もが同じ
everyone is the same.
それの色
Its color,
全て繋がる
everything connects.
夜明け また明日
Dawn, see you tomorrow.
これからも一緒に遊びましょうね
Let's keep playing together from now on.
どこまでも
No matter where,
見上げて
look up.
空から 青が降り注ぐ
Blue pours down from the sky.
繋がりは青 揺るがない言葉
The connection is blue, unwavering words.
これは始まりの物語
This is the story of the beginning.
涙は海になる
Tears turn into the ocean.
傷跡は消えない
Scars never fade.
いつまでも
Forever,
よろしくね
please treat me well.
水雲
Water clouds,
ここはステージ
here is the stage.
鳥はなき
birds sing.
私は歌う
I sing.
水面 跳ねる音
The sound of water splashing,
これからもみんなで見つけましょうね
let's keep finding it together.
どこまでも
No matter where,
探して
search.
見つけて
Find.
くれてありがとう
Thank you for finding it.
空と海 青 全て繋がってる
Sky and ocean, blue, everything is connected.
これは終わらない物語
This is an unending story.
笑顔が空になる
Smiles become the sky.
傷跡は消えない
Scars never fade.
いつまでも よろしくね
Forever, please treat me well.
皆と出会った日々いとおしくって 皆と夢叶えていきたくって
The days I met you were so precious, wanting to make dreams come true with everyone...
新しい想いでもっと 見上げて
with brand new feelings, looking up even more.
空から 青が降り注ぐ 繋がりは青 揺るがない言葉
Blue pours down from the sky, connection is blue, unwavering words.
これは始まりの物語
This is the story of the beginning.
光が増幅だす 傷跡は消えない
Light amplifies, scars never fade,
どこまでも紡ぐ 新たな未来
spinning an endless new future.
を繋いでく
...is what connects us.
二人なる
Together, we become two.
夢の数だけ夢は大きくなるんだって
Dreams grow as large as the number of dreams we have,
小さい頃から知ってたはず
I've known that since I was little.
心がブレイクしかけて立ち止まってしまっても
Even if my heart breaks and I have to stop,
ゴールは逃げたりしないから
the goal won't run away from me.
一歩ずつ ゆっくりでも
Taking it one step at a time, even slowly,
進むこと 前だけ見ていて
moving forward, keeping my eyes ahead.
辛くても 絶対に諦めないって
Even when it's hard, I'll never give up,
だっておおきな仲間がいつもそばにいるから
because my precious friends are always by my side.
明日への境界線を みんなでせーので!越えたい
Let's all cross the boundary line to tomorrow!
繋がる絆は離れない ずっと
The bonds that connect us will never separate, ever.
空回りが雨降らし つめこむこともあるけど
Even if our efforts bring rain and cause trouble,
絶対 大丈夫!
it's definitely going to be alright!
そう仲間を信じて進め
Trust in our friends and keep moving forward.
絆が深まるほど夢は確信に変わる
The deeper the bonds, the more dreams turn into certainty.
素敵な未来を描こうね
Let's paint a wonderful future.
ひとつずつ 怖がらずに
Without fear, one by one,
越えなくちゃいけない 空見上げて
look up at the sky, we have to cross over.
闇もいつかは晴れるからね
Darkness will eventually clear up, too.
道に迷って落ち込む私を照らしてくれる
Illuminating me when I get lost and fall behind on the road.
夢との境界線へ みんなでせーので!飛び込もう
Let's all leap into the boundary line of dreams!
想いを繋げて未来まで続け
Connecting our thoughts, continuing into the future.
遠回りが風吹かし 倒れることもあるけど
Even if taking the long way brings wind and makes us fall,
ずっと一緒だよ
we are always together.
さあ描いた夢まで進め
Now, let's advance to the dream we drew.
明日への境界線を みんなでせーので!越えたい
Let's all cross the boundary line to tomorrow!
繋がる絆は離れない ずっと
The bonds that connect us will never separate, ever.
どんな未来が待っていても 必ず隣にいるよ
No matter what future awaits us, I'll always be by your side.
どうか忘れないで
Please don't forget.
さあ明日を迎えに行こう
Now, let's go welcome tomorrow.
明日への境界線を みんなでせーので!越えたい
Let's all cross the boundary line to tomorrow!
繋がる絆は離れない ずっと
The bonds that connect us will never separate, ever.
どんな未来が待っていても 必ず隣にいるよ
No matter what future awaits us, we'll always be standing side by side.
どうか忘れないで
Please, don't ever forget.
さあ明日を歌にしていこう
Now, let's go toward tomorrow together!
みんな この曲はチュッチュルっていう曲だよ
Everyone, this song is a chu-chu-lu song!
手拍子とかコメントとか たくさん一緒に楽しんでくれると
If you can enjoy it together with finger snaps and comments,
とっても嬉しいです!
I'll be so, so happy!
傷つかない人など この世にいないから
There's no one in this world who never gets hurt,
たまには本当の声を聞かせてよ
so sometimes, let me hear your true voice.
あなたはまだ不器用な狼
You're still such a clumsy wolf.
もういいよ 気付かないふりして
Enough already, pretending not to notice.
深く深く愛してよ
Love me deeply, deeply.
水も甘いもメモリーヤ
The sweet and sour memories...
恋は怖くないんだよ
Love isn't scary at all,
あなたなら大丈夫
you'll be just fine.
強く強く剥がしてよ あの夜にさよならを
Peel it off strong and firm, and say goodbye to that night!
いつもここで待ってるよ だからもっと恐れずに愛してね
I'm always waiting right here, so love me even more without fear!
チュルチュルチュ チュルチュルチュ
Churuchuruchu, churuchuruchu...
誰もが一人だけじゃ いられない生き物の
No one can live all alone by themselves,
弱さを認め合い 傷付け合うものよ
we acknowledge each other's weaknesses and hurt one another.
私もまだ不器用な天使
I'm still such a clumsy angel.
お願いよ 翼を広げて
I beg you, spread your wings wide.
高く高く飛んでくよ 目指すのはサンクチュアリ
Fly high, high up into the sanctuary we aim for!
二人だけの楽園で 甘い果実狩り
Harvesting sweet fruits in our private paradise.
手と手ギュッと繋いでよ
Hold my hands tightly together,
じゃなきゃ離れちゃうから
or else we might drift apart!
ずっとここで一緒だよ だからもっと恐れずに愛してね
We'll always be together here, so love me without any fear!
チュルチュルチュ チュルチュルチュ
Churuchuruchu, churuchuruchu...
いつかできた傷跡に 涙が染みちゃうのなら
If tears soak into the scars formed someday,
笑顔のバンドエイドをあげるから 前を向いてさあ行こう
I'll give you a smiling band-aid, so look ahead and let's go!
深く深く愛してよ 何もかもがメモリーヤ
Love me deeply, deeply, everything is a memory!
恋は怖くないでしょ
Love isn't scary, right?
あなたと私なら
If it's you and me.
強く強く剥がしてよ あの夜にさよならを いつもここで待ってるよ
Peel it off strong and firm, say goodbye to that night, I'm always waiting here!
だからもっと恐れずに愛してね
So love me even more without fear!
チュルチュルチュ チュルチュルチュ
Churuchuruchu, churuchuruchu...
ただいまセッティング中です しばらくお待ちください
We are currently setting up, please wait a moment.
[Title: Setting up now, please wait a moment]
皆さん、いかがでしたか?
How was it, everyone?
楽しんでいただけましたでしょうか?
Did you enjoy it?
どうせですので、あの、本日の放送
Well, since it's the very end
締めくくって最後にもう一度乾杯をしておきましょう。
of today's broadcast, let's do one more toast!
乾杯!
Cheers!
美味しい!
Ah, delicious!
美味しいですね。
Delicious!
ねえ、今度は皆さん同じ飲み物ですよね。
Right? Everyone has the same drink too.
ねえ、そうですよねえ。
That's right, isn't it?
ねえ、この観て下さってる方も一緒に水分補給してください。
And to everyone watching, please stay hydrated too!
オリジナル曲パート最高でした!
The original song part was the best!
ああ、嬉しいです。
Ah, I'm glad.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you!
乾杯もありがとうございます。
Thank you for the toast too!
乾杯、乾杯。
Cheers!
乾杯!
やったあ、嬉しい、嬉しい。
Yay, I'm so happy.
ねえ、たくさんありがとうございます。
Thank you so much, everyone!
うんうん、ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much!
あ、お二人ともお疲れ様でしたって。ありがとうございます。
And if you're both tired, thank you so much!
プランク効きましたよね。
Prank came through, didn't it?
なかなかにね、もう焦りました。
Quite, right? I was already panicking.
え、ここで来ると思って。
I thought, "Will I make it?"
ねえ、大変でしたけど。なんとか、なんとか乗り切れましたね。
Well, it was tough, but we somehow managed to pull through.
続けたいなと思いました。
I wanted to keep going!
やあ、嬉しいです、ありがとうございます。
Yay, I'm so glad, thank you!
あの、本日改めてまして今日は、あの、ありがとうございました。
And once again, thank you so much for today!
ライブは久しぶりでは、あの、あったんですけれど、
It's been a while since our last live,
最高のお時間を皆様にお届けできたかなと思っております。
and I'm so glad we could deliver such a great time to everyone.
ねえ、それでは最後になりますが、
So, as we finally reach the end,
そらちゃん、ラミィちゃん、本日の放送はいかがでしたでしょうか?そらちゃん。
Sora-chan, Lamy-chan, how was today's broadcast? Sora-chan?
はい。
Yes!
でもなんか、ちょっとね、久しぶりのライブだったので緊張してたんですけど、
Well, since it's been a while since our last live, I was quite nervous,
3人で凄くね、あの、わちゃわちゃとお喋りもできたし、ライブもできたし、最高の時間だったなと思います。
but the three of us got to chat and have fun, sing live, and I think it was the best time.
美味しい飲み物もいっぱいもらっちゃって、
And getting to drink delicious beverages,
もう言うことないです!
there's really nothing more to say!
皆さん、観てくれてありがとうございます。
Everyone, thank you so much for watching!
そしてゲストに呼んでいただいたり、ありがとうございます。
And thank you to our guest, Lamy-chan!
とっても楽しかったです!
It was so, so fun!
やったあ、ありがとうございます、やったあ。
Yay, thank you so much, so happy!
それではラミィちゃん、本日の放送はいかがでしたでしょうか?
And Lamy-chan, how was today's broadcast?
もう今日は本当に面白かったです!
Well, today was genuinely so much fun!
なんかね、もうノムちゃんが初めてやったんですけど、
You know, Nomu-chan was hosting for the first time,
もう凄く面白くて、あっという間に時間が過ぎちゃったのもあるし、
and it was so much fun that time just flew by,
もうそら先輩とね、こうやって一緒に、そら先輩とノムちゃんと同じステージでね、歌ったりできるのがもう本当に夢みたいで楽しかったです。
getting to sing on the same stage with Sora-senpai like this was like a dream and so much fun.
ありがとうございました。
Thank you so much!
いや、あの私も本日こう、そらちゃんとラミィちゃんとご一緒できて嬉しかったのは、こう3人の並びがまた統一感があって、
Well, as for me, getting to be with Sora-chan and Lamy-chan today was so wonderful.
本当に本日のミニライブにぴったりだったなと思いますし、
It really suited today's mini-live,
こうワールドウルフでね、お互いをちょっと疑いあったりもしましたし。
we even sang World's Umily and joked around with each other!
あの本当にこう最後のトーク、テーマのトークも楽しくお話しができて、本当に、お二方のことをより知ることができて嬉しかったです。
I'm just so glad we could have such a fun talk segment at the end,
はい、皆様も遊びに来てくださって本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you so much for coming to hang out with us, everyone!
そして、あの今日せっかくこうして、あの3人が集まりましたので、
And since the three of us are gathered here today,
最後にこう3人で1曲、はい、3人で1曲歌を歌って、あの皆様とお別れをさせていただきましょうか!
let's sing one final song together as the three of us to say goodbye to everyone!
やったあ!
Yay!
いぇーい!
コメント、あ、ねえ、またやってほし、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for all the comments!
ねえ、ぴったり、この色ぴったりありがとうございます。
This color suits us so well, thank you!
ありがとう。
Thank you!
はい、たくさんコメントいただいて、ねえ、楽しかったよってありがとうございます。
Thank you for all your comments, it was so much fun!
さあ、
Now then,
あ、じゃあ、あの曲に移る前に、そらちゃんとラミィちゃんの皆様にお伝えする告知などありましたらお伺いします。
before we move on to the song, let me share some announcements from Sora-chan and Lamy-chan if they have any.
お願いします。
Yes!
じゃあそらちゃんからいきましょうか。
Let's start with Sora-chan.
はい、私はですね、え、5月15日のお誕生日に合わせて、
Yes, I will be releasing a single
え、あとはビクターエンタテインメントさんからシングルを出すんですけども、
produced by Victor Entertainment,
そのシングルの、え、受注販売が今、始まっております。
and pre-orders for that single have just started today!
全力でステージと思っているのでぜひ見ていただけたらとっても嬉しいです！
I'm giving it my all on stage, so I'd be so happy if you all check it out!
今日見てくださった皆さん本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much to everyone who watched today!
みんなのコメントもとっても楽しそうで見てて私がとってもね、ウキウキになりました！
Everyone's comments looked so fun, it made me really excited watching them!
もう終わっちゃうのは寂しいですが最後まで全力で盛り上げたいと思うので
It's sad that it's already ending, but I want to hype it up until the very end,
今日は本当に本当に最後まで楽しんでいってください！本当にありがとうございました！
so please enjoy yourselves to the absolute fullest today! Thank you so much!
それではラミィちゃんお願いします！
Now, Lamy-chan, please!
3月19日、20日の間、幕張メッセ国際展示場で
From March 19th to 20th, at Makuhari Messe International Exhibition Hall,
ホロライブ スーパーエキスポ 2022 サポーテッド バイ ヴァイスシュヴァルツを開催します！
we will hold "Hololive Super Expo 2022 Supported by Weiss Schwarz"!
また、同期間幕張メッセのイベントホールで音楽ライブ
Also, during the same period, at Makuhari Messe Event Hall,
ホロライブ3rdフェス リンクユアウィッシュ サポーテッドバイヴァイスシュヴァルツも開催しますのでぜひぜひチェックしてみてください！
"Hololive 3rd Fes. Link Your Wish," so please be sure to check it out!
私とラミィと、そら先輩ももちろん、3rdフェスに出演します！
Me, Lamy, and Sora-senpai will of course perform at the 3rd Fes!
公演に関するハッシュタグは共通で「#つながるホロライブ」です！
The common hashtag for the concert is "#TsunaGaruHololive"!
ライブのチケットやライブの配信チケットなど詳細は特設ホームページをチェックしてください！
Please check the special homepage for details on live tickets and streaming tickets!
青色配信中です！
Ao-iro is currently streaming!
ぜひ聴いてください！
Please be sure to listen!
サントリーのむプレゼント、ウィンターミニライブ本日の最後の曲を聴いてください！
Please listen to the final song of today's Suntory Nomu present Winter Mini Live!
時の空と雪花ラミィとサントリーのむで、スノーハレッサ！
"Snow Halessa" by Tokino Sora, Yukihana Lamy, and Suntory Nomu!
伸びた人影を 舗装道にならべ
Our shadows stretch out on the pavement
夕闇のなかを 君と歩いている
As I walk in the twilight with you
手をつないで いつまでもずっと そばにいれたなら
If we could be together like this forever, holding hands...
泣けちゃうくらい
It's almost enough to make me cry.
風が冷たくなって
The wind grows colder
冬の匂いがした
I can smell winter in the air.
そろそろこの街に
Soon the season will come to this town
君と近付けれる季節がくる
When I can get close to you.
今年最初の雪の華を ふたり寄り添って
Cuddle up together to gaze at the first snow flower of the year,
眺めているこの時に 幸せがあふれ出す
This moment overflows with happiness.
甘えとか弱さじゃない ただ、君を愛している
It's not dependence or weakness, I just love you.
心からそう思った
I thought so with all my heart.
君がいると どんなことでも 乗り越えられるような気持ちになってる
I feel like when I'm with you, I can overcome anything.
こんな日々が いつまでもきっと 続いていくことを祈っているよ
I pray that these days will continue forever.
風が窓を揺らし 夜は揺り起こして
The wind rattled the window, the night shakes you awake,
どんな悲しいことも 僕が笑顔へと変えてあげる
I will change any sorrow into a smile.
舞い落ちてきた雪の華が 窓の外ずっと
The snow flowers fell outside the window unceasing,
降りやまうことを知らずに 僕らの街を染める
And colored our town without knowing when they'd stop.
誰かのために何かをしたいと思えるのが
I realized that love means wanting to do something for someone else.
愛ということを知った
That's what love is.
もし、君を失ったとしたら
If I should lose you,
星になって君を照らすだろう
I'll become a star and shine on you.
笑顔も涙に濡れている夜も いつでもそばにいるよ
I'll be with you even on nights when your smile is wet with tears.
星の街路樹 君と歩く街
I walk with you through the street lined up with trees,
笑った途端 白い息が 凍えそう
And when I laughed, it looked like my white breath was going to freeze.
Ah どうして
Ah, why is it
今日も冗談ばかりで
that you're only making jokes today too?
相変わらず 微妙な距離
Our distance remains as awkward as ever...
もどかしくて 切ないけれど
It's frustrating and a bit heartbreaking,
巡る巡る 冬の夜も 今年はあったかいね
but as winter nights turn, this year feels so warm.
苦手だった 寒さだって なんだか嬉しくて
Even the cold I hated somehow feels so nice,
「遠回りしよう」君から 言わないかな
Hoping you'd say, "Let's take the long way home."
これが恋か 恋じゃないか どっちだって構わない
Whether this is love or not, it doesn't matter either way.
不器用でも ケンカしても やっぱり君がいい
Clumsy or arguing, you're still the one I want.
降り出した雪に 願いをかけるよ
I make a wish upon the falling snow,
あとちょっと このままで ふたりきり
Hoping just a little longer, we can be alone together.
ふざけたふりで 指が触れたとき
When our fingers touched as we pretended to joke around,
世界がふッと 色を変えた その瞬間
In that instant, the world suddenly changed its colors.
Ah ちょうどいいサイズ 君と私たちの手
Ah, our hands are just the perfect size for each other—
こんなふうに 繋ぐことが とっくに決まってたみたい
It feels like it was meant to be that we'd hold hands like this.
巡る巡る 冬のページ 泣いたり笑ったり
Turning the pages of winter, we cried and laughed.
思いがけず ふたりだけの 秘密が増えていく
Unexpectedly, our private secrets between just us keep growing.
いつもより胸の鼓動が うるさいけれど
My heartbeat is louder than usual, but—
これが恋か 恋じゃないか どっちだって構わない
Whether this is love or not, it doesn't matter either way.
一途すぎて はみ出しても やっぱり君がいい
Even if my devotion overflows, you're still the one I want.
降りしきる雪に 願いをかけるよ
I make a wish upon the falling snow,
あとちょっと このままで ふたりきり
Hoping just a little longer, we can be alone together.
巡る巡る 君と私 今年も来年も
Round and round, you and me, this year and next year too—
春も夏も 秋も冬も 一緒にいれるかな
Will we be able to stay together through spring, summer, autumn, and winter?
素直に言葉にできない 私だけど
Even though I can't express my feelings honestly,
これが恋か 恋じゃないか 本当は分かってる
I actually know whether this is love or not.
意地を張って 強がっても やっぱり君がいい
Even when I'm stubborn and act tough, you're still the one I want.
降り積もる雪に 願いをかけるよ
I make a wish upon the piling snow,
ずっとずっと このままで そばにいて
Hoping you'll stay by my side like this forever and ever.
番組は終了しました ご視聴ありがとうございました
The broadcast has ended. Thank you for watching.